Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
Then I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We'll live in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
But we don't want to live ordinary life.
But we have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Whoa, look at that!
Tears are making a rainbow!
The film is crying, we'll drown here!
It's practically a waterfall.
So sad!
Master Froggy!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Ahhhh!
Ahhhhh!
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Ahhhhhhhh!
Ahhhhhhh!
Dory!
You're alive!
I must've lost consciousness
Mr.
Zero
I've heard that name somewhere before.
Wasn't that the name of the boss
guy that Vivi was so frightened of?
Which would mean that the person who was
on the other end of this transponder scale
is one of the seven warlords of the sea.
It's been a long time since
I issued your orders, Mr.
Three.
What's happening on that island?
All right, so I guess this Mr.
Three character is the owner
of this transponder snail.
I think I have this figured out now.
This little place here is an enemy
hideout, and someone named Mr.
Three was ordered by someone named Mr.
Zero to come to this island
and kill Vivi. Damn it!
What was I thinking?
This was no time for me to
be out on a hunting trip.
I hope that they're all still okay.
Shit.
Well, are you going to answer me?
When I ask a question, I expect an answer.
Have you eliminated Princess Phoebe
and the Straw Hats as you were ordered?
Oh, yeah.
The mission was successful.
I eliminated all those pesky
brats like you said to.
Your secret is completely protected,
so there's no need to keep going
after them anymore. I see. So,
as we speak,
the Unluckies are headed your way in order
to confirm the success of your mission.
And to deliver a certain package.
The unluckies, of course.
And a package?
It's an eternal pose that will
point you to Alabasta Kingdom.
Once that arrives, you and Miss
Golden Week will head for Alabasta.
It's time for the next phase of the plan.
We are about to begin, embarking upon
our most important operation to date.
Details will follow
after you reach Alabasta.
Wait for my orders.
What the?
What are those?
Mr.
Three, what was that?
Oh, uh, it's nothing, really.
What the hell is that?
So I guess you're trying to kill me, huh?
Well, monkey, bring it on!
All right, you, what now?
So what are you going to do
now, you oversized chicken?
Hey, what's going on?
Answer me, Mr. Three.
Hey, well, nothing.
It's just...
that damn Straw Hat was still alive.
It's okay, though.
I finished him off real good.
No need to worry.
What do you mean, he was still alive?
I believe that just a moment ago you said
that your mission was
completed successfully.
Isn't that correct?
Yes, that is what I said.
I mean, I absolutely thought
that it was completed then,
but that Straw Hat guy is really
a lot tougher than you'd expect.
So let me see, if I understand.
The report you gave me was a complete lie?
Well, yeah.
When you put it that way, I guess
the report wasn't the truth.
But, now I've gotten rid
of that Straw Hat for sure,
so there's no need for you to send
anyone else after him or the others.
Very well.
Take the pose and head straight to
Alabasta from there immediately.
Do you understand me?
But, how are you still alive?
The weapons.
They saved me.
Weapons?
Oh, yeah!
That makes sense!
Not even weapons that were made
in Elbath could hold up after
a hundred years of giants
dueling to the death with them!
They must be dull by now!
Now that's a relief.
It's a miracle, really.
Broggy, would you let go?
I'm a little sore here.
I'm so glad you're still
alive, Dorry! It's amazing!
Come on, this wasn't a miracle.
The fact that those weapons
are even intact after
a century of fighting
is the miraculous part.
They should be scrapped by now.
I'm surprised they lasted this long.
What a day this was!
Thank you, god of Elbat,
for this wonderful day!
Oh?
Is that true, Broggy?
You're saying that fighting
me while I was injured,
Cutting me down and knocking
me out was all wonderful.
Don't be an idiot, Dory.
That's not what I'm saying and you know it
Would you keep your hands off my wounds?
You try doing that again
and see how far you get?
I can take you down in a heartbeat!
Wait!
You two are fighting again already?!
We'll have no more radio
contact from now on, understand?
If the Marines were to catch on to what
we're doing, that would be most unfortunate.
From this point on,
all of my orders will be sent via
letter, following the usual protocol.
That will be all, Mr.
Three.
Good luck on your mission.
Miss Allsunday.
Yes, sir?
I want you to send Mr.
Two to Little Garden immediately.
Mr.
Three is on his way from
Little Garden to Alabasta.
I want you to see that he is eliminated.
Perhaps that might be a
little extreme, Crocodile.
We still have plenty of agents to spare.
Are you arguing with me, Miss Allsunday?
No.
I'll make the arrangements at once.
Consider it done.
Well, he finally hung up.
Now, I wonder who these guys were.
They sure are funny looking.
What's this?
Captain Smoker, I've just
intercepted a very intriguing signal.
What is it?
Such an incredible full temper.
The legendary Kashi!
Tashigi! Tashigi!
Only here in the Grand Line could I find
such a prized sword as this so quickly!
Tashigi! Come here!
Are you dead?
Yes, they're coming, Captain!
Stop clowning around and get over here!
I need you to listen to this!
Listen close.
We just picked up this
conversation minutes ago.
I've got it all queued up.
Ready, Sergeant Major? Uh, yes.
Lay it back, please. It's Mr. Zero.
Now quit fooling around, you jackass.
Have you eliminated Princess Phoebe
and the Straw Hats as you were ordered?
Straw Hats?
Straw Hat Pirates! Oh, yeah.
A mission was successful.
From this point on,
all my orders will be sent via
letter following the usual protocol.
That will be all, Mr.
Three.
And the rest of the message
is undecipherable static.
It's a faint signal,
but there are key names and phrases laced
in their conversation
that clearly stood out.
Princess Vivi, Straw Hats,
Orders via Letter, and Mr. Zero.
Mr. Zero?
Could that be a codename for somebody?
In fact,
it's quite possible he
could be connected to that
suspicious swordsman we
caught earlier in Rudeness.
What did you say his name was? Mr. Eleven?
Possibly.
Part of a criminal organization that uses
numbers for codenames and
sends orders via letter.
Sound about right?
Huh.
Mr. Zero. Organization.
I have no idea what you're going on about.
Then how do you explain the letter of
detailed orders we found in your pocket?
Damn letter!
I thought I burned it!
Wait!
That's not... not mine!
That's funny.
Because we didn't actually
find anything in your pocket.
All right, then.
Princess Vivi, if I remember correctly,
she's from Alabasta, and reports
say she's currently missing.
Excuse me for interrupting, but isn't the
Alabasta Kingdom in the middle of a coup?
I wonder if this mysterious
criminal organization and the
Straw Hat Pirates could somehow
be involved in the uprising.
Who knows?
All I know for certain
is that this is the only
clue we have to the
Straw Hat's whereabouts.
This means we're going? Yes.
I want you to contact headquarters
and get an eternal pose. Yes, sir.
It's time we pay a little visit
to Alabasta, the Kingdom of Sand.
Gah, gah, gah, gah,
We've been fighting so
long that we had completely
forgotten about the bounties
that were put on our heads.
It has been a long time.
But I'm the whole reason that the Baroque
Works agents came here in the first place.
It's my fault.
None of that anymore, okay?
Yeah, come on, Phoebe.
Why are you so sad?
Here, have a rice cracker.
Uh, guys?
Where did you get those? I know.
Let's have a rice cracker party.
Rice crackers aren't
that exciting, though.
Sure they are!
We can even toast with them!
You see, nobody's blaming you.
Cheers!
Ow!
Hey, Luffy, don't do that!
Can't just go wasting food like that.
Seriously, you should know better.
Hey, what are you doing?
Who said you could have my cracker?
No, put it down!
Can you break it?
It's done!
It's mine!
My nose done! What's with you? Nothing.
Just a bug bite.
All right.
I still can't believe we have to wait here
a year just for the Log Pose to reset.
I know.
It's definitely something
we should be worried about.
All of you helped save
us from those other guys.
If we can't We would really
like to return the favor.
Well, maybe you guys can do something about
our Log Pose, so we won't be stuck here.
I'm afraid the Log Pose is the one
thing that we can't help you with.
Of course he's happy,
the big useless jerk!
He shows up after we've
taken care of everything!
What the hell is going on?
Is one of you guys Mr. Three?
Wait, and just how do you know about Mr.
Three anyway?
Oh, Nami!
You look absolutely
amazing in that outfit!
Say that again!
No, Nami.
If you stand around dressed like
that all day, you'll catch cold.
Here, take my coat. Oh, thank you.
So, I've been a little busy.
I just finished talking to that Mr.
Zero guy over a transponder snail.
Mr. Zero?
Yeah, that guy.
I was talking to him in this weird
hideout place I found in the jungle.
He thought I was some guy called Mr.
Three, and I thought it would be
a good idea to let him believe it.
And since I had him on the line, I went
ahead and told him that we were all dead.
So he thinks he doesn't have to
send people after us anymore.
So you're saying that we're
finally free of people
chasing us now that we
can't go anywhere anyway?
Oh, that is just perfect.
We can't go?
Why, is there still something
we need to take care of here?
That's a real shame after I
managed to get hold of this thing.
Uh, what?
An eternal pose to Alabasta!
All right!
Now we can set sail! Oh,
woohoo! Yes! Like a child!
I did the awesome thing would happen!
I was getting really worried, thank you!
No, no, it was all my pleasure.
I'm just glad I could
make you happy, Vivi.
Alright, everyone!
Now we're having a rice
cracker party! No way!
Look, Luffy, we don't have
enough left for a party.
There's only three. What?
It doesn't matter.
We don't have time for that anyway.
Come on now captain we don't have
time to be sitting here Zoro hold on
a sec so uh you forget about our
hunting contest nope hate to tell you
this but you lost i caught a rhino
that was this big that doesn't sound
very tasty but i guess you can it
sounds just fine to me hunting contest
hunting contest something about
that sounds familiar somehow?
Okay, giant old guys, it's really been
a lot of fun, but we gotta go! Huh?
Of course. Right.
We can tell you need to get going.
It's too bad that you
have to leave so soon.
I hope you'll get to
your homeland in time.
Me too. Thank you.
See ya!
Try not to die anymore, okay?
Waaaaaah! Master!
I'm going to go visit Elbas someday!
You just wait and see.
My catch is much bigger than yours.
You wish. This is right.
This way to see this thing.
I'm serious.
Our friends are setting sail.
That's right.
And we can't just sit here.
Not when there's a monster
waiting for them in the sea.
So, Dory, how are your wounds doing?
Bees, I think I can live with them.
It's safe to say that our
weapons are about worn through.
Any regrets?
It's difficult to give up.
I've fought with this axe for
more than a hundred years.
But if it's a sacrifice for our
friends, then it's worth it.
Yeah, I agree.
See?
I told you mine was bigger than yours.
I win!
You should look closer.
My lizard is much bigger.
What?
Are you blind or something?
My rhino is obviously so much
larger than your stupid lizard is.
It doesn't really matter.
They both look yummy.
Just shut up, Luffy!
Yours doesn't even have horns!
What does that have to do with anything?
Size!
Yours is puny!
My children, how long
are you going to fight?
What?
We don't need all of it anyway.
Just cut up what we do need so
we can get out of here already!
Right!
Of course, Nami!
Hey, Usopp, would you tell him
that I'm clearly the winner?
Nah, I really don't care.
Can't you just agree it's a tie?
I don't believe in ties.
I fight to win.
Just hurry up, you two!
Set sail!
The giant said that going straight would
take us to the western end of the island.
Hey, couldn't you guys have
gotten any more meat on board?
Yeah, right.
We can't possibly preserve
any more than this.
It would just spoil before we could eat it
are you actively trying to sink the ship?
Hey look at that it's the giants they
must have come down here to say goodbye.
A great danger still lies ahead of you it
is an obstacle that has always been here!
Trying to prevent people from
reaching the next island.
Uh... uh...
Every one of you fought like true warriors
in order to protect the pride of our duel.
And because you are willing to do that
no matter what enemy you may face...
We will never let them
destroy your pride, friends!
You must have faith in what we say!
Go straight!
No matter what happens,
keep going straight!
Understand?
Yeah! Got it!
What was that about?
I don't get it what he say?
No matter what happens, just go straight!
This is goodbye.
Let's meet again someday?
Absolutely.
Look! Over there!
Hello, Land Eater!
You will open the path!
In the name of Elbeth, you will open it!
Oh, my God.
It's the monster!
What the heck is that guy?
A goldfish?
It's a...
Giant goldfish!
Usopp, hey, start working the
runner or we're gonna be eaten!
Hurry it up!
Yeah, I know, but we have to go straight
ahead, isn't that right, Luffy? Mm-hmm.
We sure do.
Don't be a moron, Lupi!
This isn't gonna be anything
like what happened with Laboon!
Yeah, I know. Now calm down.
Here, I'll let you have
the last rice cracker.
I don't want a cracker!
If we don't turn the ship around
right now, that thing is gonna eat us!
Nami, just give it up.
Luffy, you really sure we can
trust those little pals of yours?
Yep.
Are we actually going to willingly
head straight into that beast's belly?
Uh-huh!
It's too late to turn now!
You've sure gotten a lot
bigger, Island Eater.
Filthy goldfish.
And his size isn't the only
surprising thing about him either.
There's also the dung that he
produces after he devours an island.
The size of that stuff
is quite impressive.
I recall one specimen that's
known as nothing at all island.
Yes,
we landed on it a long time ago and thought
it was real land we were standing on.
I'm beginning to feel nostalgic
watching them sail in.
I remember my old adventurous days.
The only thing that we can't pierce with
this weapon is the great
bloodstained snake.
Together our weapons form the most powerful
weapon Elbath can offer the giant spear.
Just go straight go
straight what does it matter
we've already been eaten
here straight okay just?
JUST KEEP GOING!
We're flying!
Don't bother looking back because
we're going straight ahead!
Look at us!
This is so incredible!
The sea itself!
The strength of the Elbeth warriors!
It's amazing!
Friends!
Go! Good luck!
Long ago,
the sea was ruled by
colossal swashbuckling
ruffians known as the
Giant Warrior Pirates.
Living only for the thrill
of battle and conquest,
these pirates laid waste
to all who opposed them.
They were presided over by two bosses,
Red Ogre Brogy and Blue Ogre Dory,
both exceptionally strong.
The power and influence they
held went largely unchecked,
for no other giant was their equal,
and ordinary men cowered
in their massive shadows.
This made the fact that a lone
little girl single-handedly
put an end to their attacks
all the more surprising.
Our two bosses are truly great!
Did you hear about their catch?
Yeah, I can hardly think about
anything else that's so exciting.
It's not every day someone bags a
huge sea king, and they each got one.
Now that's impressive.
Yeah, take us for example.
We're Elbath giants.
No greater warrior exists.
But even we don't come close to taking
down one of those massive beasts.
Wouldn't you say that's fair, man? Yeah!
I bet that no one's ever slayed a
bigger sea king than us a conquest
was bigger what
which one
look
at them
side by side brogy mine is slightly
bigger see keep dreaming My beat's
yours by three whole centimeters! What?!
You're joking! No!
Bosses, please!
Stop bickering!
I suppose I should mention, Broggy.
I recall something about a hunting
contest, but I can't exactly remember.
Don't worry, Dory.
The same thing goes for me.
It's Middle Mountain!
So, what do you say you and I
go ahead and finish this? Sure!
We can always think
things through after that!
Set me free.
Something has to change.
My world can be arranged.
I'll do anything as
long as you are with me.
I've grown stronger having you by my side.
We've started on an everlasting ride.
I'm invincible when your love is near.
When I'm with you, I have no fear.
Let's see how far we can make this go.
The world is ours, you just ride, I know.
I see it shine in the distance.
Glistening like water when
the sun rises in the dawn.